

ARNAUD THEISS

OA Tester





+32 474 29 37 33 arnaud.theiss@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Generalist
- Priorisation
- Bug documenting
- Communication
- User-centric

LANGUAGE

- English
- French (native)

EDUCATION

Certification

User Experience (UX)

ULB - Université Libre de Bruxelles 2020 - 2020

Certification

Multimedia production **EFPME**

2014 - 2016

Master - Population and Development sciences **ULB - Université Libre de Bruxelles** 2009 - 2011

PROFILE

I have always been a gamer. Three years ago, I discovered that creating games was even more fun! I have been using Unity to create game prototypes ever since I found a visual scripting plugin that would fill in my generalist gaps. I am enthusiastic about bringing my QA and Product Management experience along.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Letsbuild

Product Manager

2022 - 2023

- Set up and consume data analitics to identify opportunities and validate the adoption of new features.
- · Recurrent customer interviews to gather feedback, validate assumptions and test prototypes.

Product Operations

2020 - 2022

- Align teams and members through the development of a Risk Assessment process for squads.
- · Bring cohesion and spot team issues early through the development of a Happiness Survey.

Quality Assurance

2018 - 2020

- Manual and Automation testing (java, selenium).
- System, Functional, Regression, Smoke, Exploratory, E2E.
- Document and Prioritise identified bugs on Jira.

Hello Agency

Web Designer

2015 - 2016

- Design and develop newsletters for retail customers.
- Design for social media.

Graphic Designer

2014 - 2015

· Layout for print flyers for retail customers.